1/18/2021 Behance :: Work Experience

# **Pankhuri Agarwal**

Student

07234886000 pristine.space2000@gmail.com be.net/pankhuriagarwal1

Student of NIFT Banglore, Accessory designing.

Pankhuri has been a keen learner since the beginning. She does things for herself and her learning. Probably she would choose a less walked path over the laymen Walker's street! Pankhuri's Perseverance and Cooperation skills are the main attributes. It's a give and takes thing for her.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Lets Enodorse**

Graffiti Volunteer

I volunteered here for the old Gov. schools revamping project near Bannerghatta road. My work was to create graffiti that motivates, attracts and inspires students to come to school regularly and learn creatively.

September 2019 - September 2019 | Bangalore, India

# **My Captain**

## Marketing Intern

I got experience in business development, marketing, and sales, with a focus on community building and creating impact in my college. I performed digital marketing and sales and even helped in external collaborations. Even received LOR for my dedication and good performance.

April 2020 - May 2020 | Bangalore, India

# **Voice Of Margin**

Graphic designer, Content Creator, Editor

My responsibilities included research work, scriptwriting, making posts for the Instagram page, video editing, the post-production part of the Multi-Media Team along with digital illustrations, and all the graphic work. I also supervised interns under me. Even received LOR for my capability and sincerity.

July 2020 - September 2020 | India

# **Homeflic Wegrow**

Youth Leader, Graphic Designer

Here I worked in almost all the sectors of this company as a youth leader. I performed exceptionally well in the graphics team for creating multimedia posts with my original illustrations and animations, even got an internship opportunity there as a graphic designer. I managed the sales part of the courses as well. I learned a lot of tools and developed soft skills and technical skills. I'm glad to be a tribester!

# "LOR STATEMENT"-

During the whole course of the internship, she has been an active participant in all the tasks

and her ideas have been very fresh and contributing throughout. She brings positivity to the work environment and is a team player, who knows how to lead a troop. She is very punctual and meets deadlines positively. Her hard work is very well reflected in

tasks she submits and her 7 Instagram creatives were posted on our Instagram Profile.

November 2020 - December 2020 | India

1/18/2021 Behance :: Work Experience

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Methodist High School**

**Higher Secondary** 

From Nursery to Class 12th.

I took Physical Education as a subject in High School.

I took PCB along with core Hindi as my subjects in Higher Secondary.

Was awarded amongst the 10 ideals of the school for "Perseverance", in 2018.

March 2004 - May 2018 | Kanpur Cantonment, India

# **National Institute Of Fashion Technology**

**Bachelor in Accessory Designing** 

Major- Accessory Designing

Minor- Bftech-IT (Data Management) DS- Jewelry, Product Designing

July 2019 - | Bangalore, India

## **SKILLS**

Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Indesign, Adobe Photoshop, Autodesk Fusion 360, Autodesk Sketchbook, Canva, Filmora, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Powerpoint, Microsoft Word, SketchUp Pro

#### **ACCESSORY DESIGNER**

Making of Home decor products and Jewelry Designing.

#### **FASHION TECH**

Data handling, Website Development, AI in fashion

## **COMMUNICATION DESIGNER**

Illustrations, Animations, Photography, Content Creation.

Multimedia posts: (creation-to-ideation)

Concept development, Videos, Content editing, scripting.